<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Desa Wisata Tempellmahbang</string>

    <string-array name="tour_packages">
        <item>Dokar village tour</item>
        <item>Cycling tour</item>
        <item>Village experience</item>
        <item>Cooking lesson</item>
        <item>Rafting</item>
        <item>Farm field</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tours_description">
        <item>
            In the Dokar Village Tour package , tourists can explore the Candirejo Tourism Village area for one to two hours. The price for this package is IDR 150,000 per person.  "\n""\n"
            The price includes facilities in the form of gig transportation equipment, guides, as well as donations for tourist villages. If you want to join this package, the minimum number of participants is two people. "\n""\n"
            By following this package, visitors can find out about the daily lives of local residents as well as add new experiences about various things, ranging from customs, traditions, to the tumpengsari farming system."\n""\n"
            Guided by a guide, visitors will visit the location of home industry and agro-agriculture and learn to play gamelan."\n""\n"
            In addition, tourists can also pick fruits that are in season to be used as souvenirs. "\n""\n"
            Prices above do not include food. Visitors only get traditional snacks. If you want an additional lunch, visitors can add a fee of IDR 200,000 per person.
        </item>
        <item>
             This package is the same as the Dokar Village Tour package . The difference is, in this package, tourists will explore Candirejo Tourism Village by bicycle."\n""\n"
            The price of this package is IDR 150,000 with a duration of two hours. Minimum of two participants."\n""\n"
            This price does not include heavy meals. Visitors will only get traditional snacks and tea. "\n""\n"
            If you want additional heavy food, you can add an additional fee of IDR 200,000 per person.
        </item>
        <item>
            The price for the Village Experience package is more expensive than the previous two packages, which is IDR 497,500 per person. The minimum number of participants in this package is two people."\n""\n"
            If you buy this package, visitors can enjoy the beauty of natural tourism in Candirejo Tourism Village in half a day (08:00-12:00 WIB). "\n""\n"

            The journey begins with offroad using a jeep to Menoreh Hill. Arriving at the location, visitors can enjoy a stunning panoramic view of the Menoreh Hills landscape."\n""\n"
            Next, the guide will invite tourists to see Watu Kendil and take selfies there. "\n""\n"
            After being satisfied with taking selfies at Watu Kendil, visitors will be invited to see firsthand the activities of the local community.
            Starting from agriculture, farming, to picking fruits that can be brought home. "\n""\n"
            Then, the guide will take the visitors to stop at one place to change the means of transportation into a bicycle or a gig. "\n""\n"
            The journey then continued by enjoying the view of Candirejo Tourism Village, and ended at a residents house for lunch with a traditional menu.
        </item>
        <item>
            This package costs IDR 325,000 per person. With this price, visitors have got gig facilities, local guides, tea, donations, and traditional snacks. "\n""\n"
            The minimum number of participants in this package is two people. The duration of the trip is four hours."\n""\n"
            The journey will begin by exploring the Candirejo Tourism Village area using a bicycle or gig."\n""\n"
            Then rest at a local residents house while enjoying traditional snacks and drinking Javanese sugar tea. "\n""\n"
            After that, tourists together with the owner of the house or a local guide learn to cook traditional food for lunch.
        </item>
        <item>
            The price for the rafting or rafting package itself is IDR 150,000 per person. The minimum number of participants in this package is six people. "\n""\n"
            For three hours, you will explore the Elo River and the Progo River. While wading through the river, tourists will be spoiled with views of a row of beautiful cliffs. "\n""\n"
            After rafting,  visitors will be taken to eat lunch and enjoy traditional snacks.
        </item>
        <item>
            You can get various facilities when you visit here. One of them, you can interact directly with farm animals and see plantations. Apart from that, you also feed livestock, catch fish and participate in farming.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tours_price">
        <item>150000</item>
        <item>150000</item>
        <item>497500</item>
        <item>325000</item>
        <item>150000</item>
        <item>50000</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="tour_images">
        <item>@drawable/img_dokar</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_cycling</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_villagetour</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_cooking</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_rafting</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_farmfield</item>
    </array>

</resources>