<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Desa Wisata Tempellmahbang</string>

    <string-array name="tour_packages">
        <item>Dokar village tour</item>
        <item>Cycling tour</item>
        <item>Village experience</item>
        <item>Cooking lesson</item>
        <item>Rafting</item>
        <item>Farm field</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tours_description">
        <item>
            In the Dokar Village Tour package , tourists can explore the Candirejo Tourism Village area for one to two hours. "\n"
            The price for this package is IDR 150,000 per person. The price includes facilities in the form of gig transportation equipment, guides, as well as donations for tourist villages. "\n"
            If you want to join this package, the minimum number of participants is two people. By following this package, visitors can find out about the daily lives of local residents as well as add new experiences about various things, ranging from customs, traditions, to the tumpengsari farming system."\n"
            Guided by a guide, visitors will visit the location of home industry and agro-agriculture and learn to play gamelan. In addition, tourists can also pick fruits that are in season to be used as souvenirs.Prices above do not include food. Visitors only get traditional snacks. If you want an additional lunch, visitors can add a fee of IDR 200,000 per person.
        </item>
        <item>
             This package is the same as the Dokar Village Tour package . The difference is, in this package, tourists will explore Candirejo Tourism Village by bicycle."\n"
            The price of this package is IDR 150,000 with a duration of two hours. Minimum of two participants. This price does not include heavy meals."\n"
            Visitors will only get traditional snacks and tea. If you want additional heavy food, you can add an additional fee of IDR 200,000 per person."\n"
        </item>
        <item>
            3
        </item>
        <item>
            4
        </item>
        <item>
            The price for the rafting or rafting package itself is IDR 150,000 per person. The minimum number of participants in this package is six people. "\n"
            For three hours, you will explore the Elo River and the Progo River. While wading through the river, tourists will be spoiled with views of a row of beautiful cliffs. "\n"
            After rafting,  visitors will be taken to eat lunch and enjoy traditional snacks.
        </item>
        <item>
            You can get various facilities when you visit here. One of them, you can interact directly with farm animals and see plantations. Apart from that, you also feed livestock, catch fish and participate in farming.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tours_price">
        <item>150000</item>
        <item>150000</item>
        <item>497500</item>
        <item>325000</item>
        <item>150000</item>
        <item>50000</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="tour_images">
        <item>@drawable/img_dokar</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_cycling</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_villagetour</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_cooking</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_rafting</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_farmfield</item>
    </array>

</resources>